A Guide to the RADA--Richmond First Club Archives (1919- )
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Clippings and Miscellaneous Files n.d., (1963- )
  - Governor's Commission: Urban Development 1975 (Box-folder 22.61)
  - Governor's Commission: Urban Development 1975-1980 (Box-folder 22.62)
  - Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future--Doherty (Box-folder 22.7)
  - Henrico County Annual Report--Fuhrmann 1970 (Box-folder 22.8)
  - Human Needs in Housing 1964 (Box-folder 22.9)
  - James River as Common Wealth 1984 (Box-folder 22.10)
  - Major Streets and Highways, City of Richmond--Fuhrmann 1957 (Box-folder 22.11)
  - Marshaling Citizen Power to Modernize Corrections 1972 (Box-folder 22.12)
  - Mayoral Blue Ribbon Commission 1986 (Box-folder 22.13)
  - McKinsey Proposals--Doherty 1974 (Box-folder 22.14)
  - National Conference on Managed Growth--Doherty (Box-folder 22.15)
  - Need to Review Virginia's Local Government Structure 1988 (Box-folder 22.16)
  - Open Education--Doherty 1972 (Box-folder 22.17)
  - Plan of Government for the Richmond Region 1959 (Box-folder 22.18)
  - Public Utilities--Fuhrmann 1963 (Box-folder 22.19)
  - Regional Solid Waste Management Plan Draft 1984 (Box-folder 22.20)
  - Resolution: Port Authority--Fuhrmann (Box-folder 23.1)
  - Retail Trade Activity 1977-1982 (Box-folder 23.2)
  - Richmond Chamber of Commerce 1977-1978 (Box-folder 23.3)
  - Richmond Community Action Program 1986-1987 (Box-folder 23.4)
  - Richmond Dog Control Statistics--Fuhrmann 1970 (Box-folder 23.5)
  - Richmond Harbor Facts--Fuhrmann 1970 (Box-folder 23.6)
  - Richmond Magazine Article (Box-folder 23.7)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Area Archeological Survey v. 1 (Box-folder 23.8)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Area Archeological Survey v. 2 (Box-folder 23.9)
  - Richmond Metropolitan Authority--Fuhrmann 1968 (Box-folder 24.1)
  - Richmond Redevelopment and Housing Authority (Box-folder 24.2)
  - Richmond/Tri-Cities Area Resource Recovery Economic Feasibility Study 1988 (Box-folder 24.3)
  - School Board, Desegregation, Urban Planning, etc. (Box-folder 24.31)
  - School board, Integration, Concerned Citizens, etc. No. 2 (Box-folder 24.32)
  - School Board, Integration, Concerned Citizens, etc. No. 3 (Box-folder 24.33)
  - School Board, Integration, Concerned Citizens, etc. No. 4 (Box-folder 24.34)
  - School board, Integration, Concerned citizens, etc. No. 5 (Box-folder 24.35)
  - Route 288 (Box-folder 24.4)
  - Ward System--Doherty (Box-folder 24.5)
- Oversize Material
  - Three Editions of Hanover Living Guide
  - Hanover Living Guide Advertiser Directory
  - Copy of The Richmond Business Journal 12/8--14/86
  - Map: Chesterfield County, VA - Eastern Area
  - Map: Chesterfield County, VA - General Plan 2000 Update
  - Map: Thoroughfare Plan, Update 2000, County of Henrico 1984
  - Land Use Plan, Update 2000, County of Henrico 1984
  - Map: Powhite Route 288, Development Area Land Use and Transportation Plan, Chesterfield County, VA
  - Map: Goochland County Land Use Plan
- RFC 1994 75th Anniversary History
  - Draft of "A Seventy-Five Participation in Local Government" RFC history 1919-1994 by John H. Whaley, Jr. (Box-folder 25.1)
  - History Committee 1989-1990 (Box-folder 25.21)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 25.2)
  - Transcript of interivew with Susan Brown (Box-folder 25.3)
  - Transcript of interview with Robert Buford (Box-folder 25.4)
  - Transcript of interview with Jim Doherty (Box-folder 25.5)
  - Transcript of interview with Irving Held (Box-folder 25.6)
  - Transcript of interview with Ed Hirschler (Box-folder 25.7)
  - Transcript of interview with Ed Lane (Box-folder 25.8)
  - Transcript of interview with Jerry McCarthy (Box-folder 25.9)
  - Transcript of interview with Pat McSweeney (Box-folder 25.10)
  - Transcript of interview with George Peterson (Box-folder 25.11)
  - Transcript of interview with Stuart White (Box-folder 25.12)
  - Transcript of interview with Tom Yeaman (Box-folder 25.13)
- Raymond Inchbeck Collection of RFC Materials 1948-1967
  - Annual Reports 1955-1956 (Box-folder 26.1)
  - Annual Reports 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26.2)
  - Attendence 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26.21)
  - Bulletins 1957 (Box-folder 26.3)
  - Bulletins and Correspondence 1957-1958 (Box-folder 26.4)
  - Bulletins 1958-1960 (Box-folder 26.5)
  - Bulletins, reports (1 of 3) 1959 (Box-folder 26.6)
  - Bulletins, reports (2 of 3) 1959 (Box-folder 26.7)
  - Bulletins, reports (3 of 3) 1959 (Box-folder 26.8)
  - Bulletins, reports 1959-1960 (Box-folder 26.9)
  - Bulletins, reports 1963 (Box-folder 26.10)
  - Bulletins 1964 (Box-folder 26.11)
  - Bulletins, reports 1965 (Box-folder 26.12)
  - Bulletins 1966 (Box-folder 26.13)
  - Bulletins 1967 (Box-folder 26.14)
  - Correspondence 1955-1956 (Box-folder 27.1)
  - Correspondence 1956-1957 (Box-folder 27.2)
  - Correspondence 1960 (Box-folder 27.3)
  - Good Government Award - Nominations 1955 (Box-folder 27.4)
  - Good Government Award 1955 (Box-folder 27.5)
  - Good Government Award - Letters of Invitation to Special Guests 1956 (Box-folder 27.6)
  - Good Government Award 1956 (Box-folder 27.7)
  - Good Government Award 1957 (Box-folder 27.8)
  - Good Government Award 1958 (Box-folder 27.9)
  - Good Government Award 1959 (Box-folder 27.10)
  - Good Government Award - Reservations (Box-folder 27.11)
  - Minutes (1 of 2) 1954-1955 (Box-folder 28.1)
  - Minutes (2 of 2) 1954-1955 (Box-folder 28.2)
  - Minutes 1955--1956 (Box-folder 28.3)
  - Minutes (1 of 2) 1956-1957 (Box-folder 28.4)
  - Minutes (2 of 2) 1956-1957 (Box-folder 28.5)
  - Minutes (1 of 3) 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28.6)
  - Minutes (2 of 3) 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28.7)
  - Minutes (3 of 3) 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28.8)
  - Miscellaneous 1954-1955 (Box-folder 29.1)
  - Miscellaneous 1956 (Box-folder 29.2)
  - Miscellaneous (1 of 2) 1958-1959 (Box-folder 29.3)
  - Miscellaneous (2 of 2) 1958-1959 (Box-folder 29.4)
  - Miscellaneous 1960-1961 (Box-folder 29.41)
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1948 (Box-folder 29.5)
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1955 (Box-folder 29.6)
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1956-1957 (Box-folder 29.7)
  - Miscellaneous Committees and Reports 1959-1960 (Box-folder 30.1)
  - News Clippings and Miscellaneous 1956-1958 (Box-folder 30.2)
  - Old Timer's Night 1959 (Box-folder 30.3)
  - Pamphlets 1952-1956 (Box-folder 30.4)
  - Photograph: Sen. Barry Goldwater (Box-folder 30.5)
  - Recent Programs List 1955-1956 (Box-folder 30.6)
  - Administrative manual 1993 (Box-folder 31.1)
  - Associates Committee 1997 (Box-folder 31.2)
  - Attendance 1994-1995 (Box-folder 31.3)
  - Board Meetings Agendas & Notes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.4)
  - Board - Recommendations to Membership n.d. (Box-folder 31.5)
  - Board Meetings/Minutes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.6)
  - Board Meeting/Minutes 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.7)
  - Board Meeting/Minutes 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.8)
  - Board Meeting - Miscellaneous 1995-1996 (Box-folder 31.9)
  - Board - Roster 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.10)
  - Brochure 1996 (Box-folder 31.11)
  - Buddy List 1997 (Box-folder 31.12)
  - Budget 1995-1997 (Box-folder 31.13)
  - Bulletins 1996 (Box-folder 31.14)
  - Bulletins 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.15)
  - Bulletin 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.16)
  - Club Brochures n.d. (Box-folder 31.17)
  - Club History n.d. (Box-folder 31.18)
  - Club Meetings Materials 1997 (Box-folder 31.19)
  - Committees General n.d. (Box-folder 31.20)
  - Committees 1998 (Box-folder 31.21)
  - Committee Topic and Interest Survey 1993 (Box-folder 31.22)
  - Correspondence 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.23)
  - Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.24)
  - Directory n.d. (Box-folder 31.25)
  - Forms 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.26)
  - Goals/Notes 1997 (Box-folder 31.27)
  - Guest and Potential Member List n.d. (Box-folder 31.28)
  - Information re: Richmond Speakers Handouts 1997 (Box-folder 31.29)
  - Invoices/Budget 1997 (Box-folder 31.30)
  - 'Issues & Options', Vol. 1 No. 1 n.d. (Box-folder 31.31)
  - Leadership Talks 1996 (Box-folder 31.32)
  - Leadership 1998 (Box-folder 31.33)
  - League Dinner 1996 (Box-folder 31.34)
  - Letter to Mike Brooks 1997 (Box-folder 31.35)
  - Letters on Past Presidents 1993 (Box-folder 31.36)
  - Logo Designs 1993 (Box-folder 31.37)
  - Management Issue 1996 (Box-folder 31.38)
  - Margot Garcia Speakers 1997 (Box-folder 31.39)
  - Marketing 1997 (Box-folder 31.40)
  - Membership Applications n.d. (Box-folder 31.41)
  - Membership 1997 (Box-folder 31.42)
  - Membership Info n.d. (Box-folder 31.43)
  - Membership Sign-up and Attendance Lists 1995-1996 (Box-folder 31.44)
  - Membership Sign-In Lists 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.45)
  - Misc. (Minutes, Lists, Letters) 1997 (Box-folder 31.46)
  - Nominating Committee 1997 (Box-folder 31.47)
  - President's Letter 1997-1998 (Box-folder 31.48)
  - Publicity 1994-1996 (Box-folder 31.49)
  - Recruitment 1996-1997 (Box-folder 31.50)
  - Registered Agent 1997 (Box-folder 31.51)
  - Revenue Sharing Committee 1996 (Box-folder 31.52)
  - Revenue Sharing Committee 1997 (Box-folder 31.53)
  - Revenue Sharing Committee--Forum 1997 (Box-folder 31.54)
  - Richmond First Club II 1996 (Box-folder 31.55)
  - Richmond First, Extra Debate Materials 1995-1996 (Box-folder 32.1)
  - Speakers 1998 (Box-folder 32.2)
  - Treasurer/Balance Sheet 1996-1998 (Box-folder 32.3)
  - 75th Anniversary--Announcements, mailing lists, etc. 1994 (Box-folder 32.4)